<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Colvin</title>
    <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Colvin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Chris Colvin 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 14:07:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//chrismcolvin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountain Pen Experiment /3</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 14:07:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-3/</guid>
      <description>On Paper Lately at work I&amp;rsquo;ve been running into a bit of a predicament. You see, being a picket pen, I bring my Kaweco Sport with me every day. I&amp;rsquo;ve grown quite font of that little pen, and have started bringing it with me almost everywhere, along with my tiny little bullet journal. However, at work, I use these branded notepads to take notes on.
At first, I thought that the Kaweco was the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bullet Journal</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/bullet-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:01:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/bullet-journal/</guid>
      <description>Trying That Bullet Journal Thing There is no question that we live in a time when having a handwritten planner is not the norm. In fact, for a long time, I thought my mother was simply wasting her time and money on a yearly planner, going through the process of keeping a physical planner is tedious and the cost of a planner is certainly more than the to-do app on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountain Pen Experiment /2</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 14:41:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-2/</guid>
      <description>Using the Pen It&amp;rsquo;s been about three or four weeks since I got my first fountain pen, a Kaweco Sport Classic, and I thought I would share some of my thoughts and experiences thus far. Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find a bit on what it&amp;rsquo;s like to use a fountain pen day-to-day.
First off, let&amp;rsquo;s go over what I&amp;rsquo;ve been using my pen for. Being a pocket pen, this pen comes with me pretty much everywhere I go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinning Up a Hugo Blog /1</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 13:59:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Or, How I Made This Blog I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about creating a blog for a while now, but was always hesitant. For one reason or another, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I should. This was of course silly, especially given the number of articles out there that make it clear, the best way to start a blog is to start one.
One of the main reasons I never started one was because I wanted to make a blog site that was custom, easy to use, and fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountain Pen Experiment /1</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 19:46:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by pens, pencils, and other mark-making tools. However, I&amp;rsquo;ve never turned that interest into much more than a passing glance. Recently I finally decided to try something out that I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking into for some time: the fountain pen.
Being a graphic-design student, I was certainly particular about my writing and drawing tools. I picked up a lead holder, and Micron pens, both of which I still use and love, but neither of which were ever particularly great for note taking or writing for long periods of time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>