<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chris Colvin</title>
    <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chris Colvin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Chris Colvin 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 19:29:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Blog /6</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-6/photo-blog-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 19:29:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-6/photo-blog-6/</guid>
      <description>Winter is here. Hello Internet,
After the winter of 2019 finally caught up with West Michigan, I have a few photos to share from the past couple of weeks. Hopefully some of these images have captured the cold, yet scerene scenery of Grand Rapids and West Michigan during this time. Locals will know that this is only the beginning of the Midwest&amp;rsquo;s longest season, so stay tuned for more snowy pictures in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Blog /5</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-5/photo-blog-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 20:02:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-5/photo-blog-5/</guid>
      <description>Gone Hiking Hello Internet,
So I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a journey to find a new camera, and during this time I&amp;rsquo;ve been shooting a lot more than I used to&amp;hellip; and I&amp;rsquo;m loving it! I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing more hiking&amp;ndash;there&amp;rsquo;s actually some decent trails around GR&amp;ndash;so I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting to shoot a bit more landscape, which I never really did before. Anyways, it&amp;rsquo;s been a little while since I&amp;rsquo;ve posted one of these, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been shooting a lot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Blog /4</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-4/photo-blog-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 21:03:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-4/photo-blog-4/</guid>
      <description>Back to Film After finally getting around to bringing in a few of the rolls I&amp;rsquo;ve shot in the last few months, let&amp;rsquo;s get some of these shots out there! Here are a few of my favorite shots from the last few rolls of film.
This is a great example of one of the reasons I love film. That gradient on the water? That&amp;rsquo;s something I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen look quite the same in a digital image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Blog /3</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:32:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-3/</guid>
      <description>More Film on the Way But for now, here are some photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken recently. The first few photos are from my old(?) Canon T1i with a nifty-fifty (50mm f1.8). Below those you&amp;rsquo;ll see some photos from my new (old) camera, the Sony a6000. More on that another time, maybe.
Anyways, here are some images from Cascade Peace Park taken on the Canon T1i.
The forest is actually quite lovely in the winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Took So Long?</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/why-it-took-so-long/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 20:43:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/why-it-took-so-long/</guid>
      <description>Why it took me so long to start a journal. It&amp;rsquo;s 2018, I am 26 years old, and I just decided to start journaling. Why did it take me so long to start journaling, and what changed that prompted me to start? Why is something that I used to think was a waste of time, unenjoyable, and not for me now one of my favorite things to do? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at some of the main reasons I avoided journaling, and what changed my mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Interest Becomes Addiction</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/interest-addiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 19:51:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/interest-addiction/</guid>
      <description>And what to do about it. What is addiction? Taken straight from Wikipedia: &amp;ldquo;Addiction is a brain disorder characterized by compulsive engagement in rewarding stimuli despite adverse consequences.&amp;rdquo;
Just think for a few minutes about how many things in your life might fit into that category. No really, think about it. It&amp;rsquo;s probably a simpler definition than you might have expected. Now, obviously I&amp;rsquo;m looking at addiction in a pretty low level, but even so, at a low level the effects can be more than just noticeable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Blog /2</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 18:42:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-2/</guid>
      <description>Loving this film thing&amp;hellip; The more I shoot with my film cameras, the more fun I&amp;rsquo;m having, and the more I appreciate the medium. As I get more comfortable using film, hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll have more photos to share, and more variety as well.
All photos were taken with my Canon AE-1 (or AE-1 Program) with on Kodak Ultramax 400.
Enjoy!
Photo Credit: Jess Colvin
That&amp;rsquo;s it for now! Come back soon, and I&amp;rsquo;ll hopefully have more to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography and Film</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photography-and-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 21:04:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photography-and-film/</guid>
      <description>Of all the artistic mediums that I&amp;rsquo;ve tried, only one has stuck with me as something that I truly love: photography. I love photography. I also have an immense appreciation for film. And now, I&amp;rsquo;m going to delve into why that is, and maybe it will spark an interest in someone new!
I first got into photography in high-school. Like many things in my life, I got the idea to try out photography from my older brother.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Blog /1</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 11:41:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/photo-blog-1/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Been a Minute. If you&amp;rsquo;ve read my post about setting new goals this spring, you might remember that one of my goals was to shoot more photos, and share those photos in ways I haven&amp;rsquo;t done before. One of the ways I thought of to share more photos is to create photo blog posts here on my personal blog. Basically, after I get a roll of film developed, or go on a little trip somewhere, or just go for a photo walk, I&amp;rsquo;ll post my findings here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Is Here</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/spring-is-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 21:01:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/spring-is-here/</guid>
      <description>Also, Taking and Sharing Photos, and Setting New Goals Spring is finally here. It took a hot second—2018 is turning out to be a bit of a trickster. But hey, I&amp;rsquo;m so happy that it&amp;rsquo;s starting to warm up, and the sun is shining. Rain will be wecome, too, to get things growing again.
A time of renewal and growth, Spring is a great time to set new goals. I&amp;rsquo;m not one to make new years resolutions, because I know I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t keep them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is This Blog?</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 18:31:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/blog/</guid>
      <description>I write about my interests. As of right now, that is really about the gist of it! I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to start a blog for a long time. However, I never really thought I had anything worth sharing. And, honestly, not much has changed. One thing that has changed, though, is my perspective no whether or not that matters. Turns out, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t. But something does&amp;hellip;
I have a confession: I hated writing papers in high-school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fisher Space Pen</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fisher-space-pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 18:11:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fisher-space-pen/</guid>
      <description>The Fisher Space Pen is an interesting little pen. Smaller than my Kaweco Sport, it could literally fit anywhere. Which makes sense for an everyday carry inspired pen. After a recent rip to Seattle, I wanted a nice pen that was easy to travel with, and decided to pick one of these up. I thought I would share my thoughts for anyone else that might be thinking about picking on of these up as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinning Up a Hugo Blog /2</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/hugo-blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 19:09:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/hugo-blog-2/</guid>
      <description>Part 2: Installing Hugo Intro Alright, so you&amp;rsquo;re excited about creating your new website and you&amp;rsquo;re excited to give Hugo a try. Fair enough! Let&amp;rsquo;s jump right into it!
A couple things to note, though, before we get started. If you are looking for the simplest and quickest way to get Hugo up and running, look no further than Hugo&amp;rsquo;s own docs. They are fairly easy to read, and are great if you&amp;rsquo;re just looking to get into it as quickly as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountain Pen Experiment /3</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 14:07:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-3/</guid>
      <description>On Paper Lately at work I&amp;rsquo;ve been running into a bit of a predicament. You see, being a picket pen, I bring my Kaweco Sport with me every day. I&amp;rsquo;ve grown quite font of that little pen, and have started bringing it with me almost everywhere, along with my tiny little bullet journal. However, at work, I use these branded notepads to take notes on.
At first, I thought that the Kaweco was the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bullet Journal</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/bullet-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 12:01:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/bullet-journal/</guid>
      <description>Trying That Bullet Journal Thing There is no question that we live in a time when having a handwritten planner is not the norm. In fact, for a long time, I thought my mother was simply wasting her time and money on a yearly planner, going through the process of keeping a physical planner is tedious and the cost of a planner is certainly more than the to-do app on your phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountain Pen Experiment /2</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 14:41:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen-2/</guid>
      <description>Using the Pen It&amp;rsquo;s been about three or four weeks since I got my first fountain pen, a Kaweco Sport Classic, and I thought I would share some of my thoughts and experiences thus far. Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find a bit on what it&amp;rsquo;s like to use a fountain pen day-to-day.
First off, let&amp;rsquo;s go over what I&amp;rsquo;ve been using my pen for. Being a pocket pen, this pen comes with me pretty much everywhere I go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spinning Up a Hugo Blog /1</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 13:59:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Or, How I Made This Blog I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about creating a blog for a while now, but was always hesitant. For one reason or another, I just didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like I should. This was of course silly, especially given the number of articles out there that make it clear, the best way to start a blog is to start one.
One of the main reasons I never started one was because I wanted to make a blog site that was custom, easy to use, and fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fountain Pen Experiment /1</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 19:46:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/fountain-pen/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by pens, pencils, and other mark-making tools. However, I&amp;rsquo;ve never turned that interest into much more than a passing glance. Recently I finally decided to try something out that I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking into for some time: the fountain pen.
Being a graphic-design student, I was certainly particular about my writing and drawing tools. I picked up a lead holder, and Micron pens, both of which I still use and love, but neither of which were ever particularly great for note taking or writing for long periods of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 20:06:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//chrismcolvin.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description> Hello World </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>